Guide to the Human Rights Campaign records, 1975-2015.
Human Rights Campaign records, 1975-2015
- Series III. Legislative and Public Policy, 1975 -
  - Public Policy Department, Administrative and Subject Files, 1975-1995
    - HRCF PPD- "Get A LEGislative Update"- daily, Jan- Oct 1994 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - 103rd Congress - clippings, reports, memos, Mar 1993 - Sept 1994, 1993-94 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - HRCF Public Policy Division, 1993-94 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - HRCF Public Policy Div - materials, correspondence [D. Zingale], 1994 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - HRCF PPD - Lobby Visit Response Report Sheets, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - HRCF PPD - internal memos, corresp., Aug 1993-Sept 1994 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Congressional Hearing on Accreditation of Graduate Medical Education, June 1995 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Congressional Hearing on H.R. 1946- Parental Rights and Responsibility Act of 1995 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Condom Availability in Schools (MA) Curtis vs. Falmouth, 1992-95 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Brown v. Hot, Sexy, and Safer Productions (MA), 1993-1995 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Brown v. Hot, Sexy, and Safer Productions (MA) U.S. Court of Appeals, 1st Circuit, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - "Parents, Schools, and Values," Hearings- Witness Testimony, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - "Parental Involvement" Hearings- Potential Witnesses, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - "Parents, Schools, and Values" Testimony- William Bennett, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - "Parents, School, and Values" Hearing- Testimony & Background Info, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - "Parents, Schools, and Values" Hearing- Testimony and background info, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - HRC & Allied Orgs. Response: Hoekstra Hearing Info, memos, etc., 1995 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - "Parents, Schools, and Values" Hearing HRC Response, Talking points, and Potential Questions for witnesses, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Hearings- Organizational letters to Hoekstra Individual letters to Hoekstra, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - CUAV- Community United Against Violence- AIDS Education, 1994-95 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - HRC Website during Hearings, Sept. - Dec 1995 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Action Alerts from Other Orgs., Fall 1995 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - "Parents, Schools, and Values" Hearing- Organizational Responses to hearings/ issues, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - The G/L Resource Center of Ventura County (press releases, newsletters, policies, letters), 1987-95 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Alone no more: Developing a School Support System for G/L/B Youth Publication by Minnesota Dept. of Education, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Homosexuality in Schools/ G/L/B Students, 1993-95 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Family Life Education, Fairfax County, VA, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - L/G/B Students/ School Issues- State level Action, Policies, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - "Safe Schools Anti-Violence Project" Annual Reports, Seattle. WA, 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - MA- Governor's Commission on Gay & Lesbian Youth, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - MA- Safe Schools Program for Gay and Lesbian Students, 1994-95 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Project 10 East- Cambridge Public Schools, 1993-1995 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Youth Project 10- Los Angeles Schools, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Lesbian/ Gay Speakers Bureau- Training Manual (San Francisco), 1995 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Report: Saint Paul, mp, Public Schools- "Out for Equity", July 1995 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - HRCF - Correspondence - Gay Cable Network, Dec. 1986-March 1987 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - HRCF - "Presidential Classroom for Young Americans" letter - Reckitt (ed), 1987 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - HRCF--Youth Board, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Gainesville Area Human Rights Campaign, "Information Packet on Sexual Orientation & Human Rights", Ca. 1992 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - ENDA Working Notes- California (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Working Notes- Colorado (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - ENDA Notes- Massachusetts (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - ENDA Working Notes- Oregon, Penn (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - ENDA Working Notes- general HRC Correspondence, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Misc. Legal legislation- Civil Rights (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - DP- Employees, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Domestic Partnership (DP) Employee Considerations (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Project Wall Street "1993 Census", 1994 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Sexual Orientation Discrimination- Reports, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - HRCF "Documenting Discrimination" 1st Ed. (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - HRCF "Documenting Discrimination" 2nd Ed. Originals, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Romer v. Evans Legal Materials, 1994-5 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - ENDA Color Blind Initiative (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - ENDA Religious Support, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Civil Rights Law- State Executive Orders, 1994-96 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Civil Rights documentation- articles, 1994-96 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Workplace Orientation policies- publications, 1993-1994 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - ENDA Corporate Endorsement, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Work Place Project- Organizational/Business Responses, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - HRCF "Documenting Discrimination" Personal Stories of Employment Discrimination - final version, 1994-1995 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - HRC Press Release & Talking Points Employment Discrimination, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Employers with non-Discrimination Policies (Governmental & Law Firms), 1995-96 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Civil Rights Bill Jurisdictions with non-Discrimination statutes, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Civil Rights Bill Documenting- Corporate, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - HR 1863 (104TH Cong. 1st Session) House Language- ENDA, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - H.R. 4636 (103RD Congress, 2nd session) House Language- ENDA, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Los Angeles County Bar Association Committee on Sexual Orientation Bias Report, June 1994 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Los Angeles County Bar Association Committee on Sexual Orientation Bias Appendices to Report, June 1994 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Civil Rights Bill Documenting-Summary of State Provisions, Ca.1994 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Civil Rights Legislation-MA, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Civil Rights Legislation-WI, 1990-1991 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Civil Rights Legislation/reports-CA, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Civil Rights Legislation/reports -IA, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Civil Rights Legislation/reports -PA, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Civil Rights Legislation/reports-CT, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Civil Rights Legislation/reports-NYC, 1983-85 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Civil Rights Legislation/reports-MD (Baltimore), 1993 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Civil Rights Legislation/reports-MN, 1989-1993 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - 103rd Congress- AIDS/HIV policy discussions, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - HRCF F.A.N.- 103rd Congress issues/ alerts (FAN publications), 1994 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - HRCF Ballot measure Campaign, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - HRCF Abrea- corresp., calendar, memos, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - Leadership 2000 (Democratic Leaders) Conference, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - 103rd Congress News Clippings - gay/lesbian, Aug - Oct 1993 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - 103rd Congress News Clippings - gay/lesbian, Sept - Dec 1993 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - 103rd Congress News Clippings - gay/lesbian, Jan - Mar 1994 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - 103rd Congress News Clippings - gay/lesbian, Mar - June 1994 (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - 103rd Congress News Clippings - gay/lesbian, Apr - Dec 1994 (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - HRCF Public Policy Division - 103rd cong. Issues (memos, reports, PPD efforts), 1993 (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - HRCF Press Releases, Sept- Nov 1993 (Box 12, Folder 54)
    - HRCF Press Releases, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 55)
    - People of Color- memos, correspondence, etc, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 56)
    - People of Color- publications, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 57)
    - HRCF Congressional Policies- non-discrimination pledges, 1993-94 (Box 12, Folder 58)
    - Voting Records of 103rd Congress (votes per bill), 1993-94 (Box 12, Folder 59)
    - ENDA (Employment Non-Discrimination Act) and Equality Agenda, 1999 (Box 85)
    - Senators' Files, 1989-2002 (Box 86)
    - Proposed State Legislative Electoral Pilot Plan, May 2005 (Box 127, Folder 12)
    - HRC's Political Action Committee (Box 127, Folder 14)
  - Legislative Reports and Weekly Updates, 1988-1991
    - HRCF Legislative Reports and Weekly Updates, Aug 1988 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - HRCF Legislative Reports and Weekly Updates, June-December 1989 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - HRCF Legislative Reports and Weekly Updates, Jan-Feb 1990 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - HRCF Legislative Reports and Weekly Updates, March-April 1990 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - HRCF Legislative Reports and Weekly Updates, May-July 1990 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - HRCF Legislative Reports and Weekly Updates, August-October 1990 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - HRCF Legislative Reports and Weekly Updates, March-April 1991 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - HRCF Legislative Reports and Weekly Updates, May-June 1991 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - HRCF Legislative Reports and Weekly Updates, July-Sept. 1991 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - HRCF Legislative Reports and Weekly Updates, Oct.-Dec. 1991 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Organizational Subject Files Inherited from GRNL, 1976-1988
    - AIDS Action Network, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - American Legislative Exchange Council, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - American Psychological Association- Comm. on Gay Affairs, 1980-82 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Americans for Democratic Action--1983 ADA National Convention, 1982-83 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Anti-Gay Organizations-Against D.C. AIDS Legislation, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Bay Area Physicians or Human Rights, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - ACLU Bill of Rights Lobby, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - BWMT--Black and White Men Together, 1982-83 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - CDC Conference on Anti-Body Testing, Feb 1987 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Congressional Black Caucus, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Desert & Mountain States Lesbian & Gay Conference, May 1988 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - HRCF-East End Organization for Human Rights (N.Y.), 1986 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - National Conference of Gay and Lesbian Public Officials, Nov 1988 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Emily's List, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Equity Institute- Diversity Training in Schools, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - HRCF-FAIR-PAC, 1984-1985 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - HTG- Hi-Tech Guys Newsletter (San Jose, CA), Oct 1987 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - FF-1st National Lesbian and Gay Education Conference, July 1988 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Lambda Legal Defense Fund- AIDS update vol. 3, No. 1 Docket update Sept. 1988 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Lavender Law Conference, Nov 1988 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - GRNL-Leadership Conference on Civil Rights, 1982-86 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Third Annual Louisiana AIDS Conference, June 1988 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - HRCF-March on Washington for Lesbian and Gay Rights, Oct 11 1987, 1986-87 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - HRCF-"Out in the Heartlands: Taking the next step" Midwest Regional Leadership Conference, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - NARAL- Nat'l Abortion Rights League- grassroots organizing and training, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - National AIDS Network, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - National AIDS Vigil Commission, Oct 1983 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - National Association of Gay and Lesbian Dem. Clubs, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - National Black Gay & Lesbian Conference, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - National Committee for an Effective Congress-Listing of Contests, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - National Coalition of Black Gays, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - National Gay Rights Advocates, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - National Lesbian and Gay Health Foundation, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - NOW-ERA National Outreach Campaign Kit, 1981-82 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - NOW (Nat'l Org. for Women), 1976, 1983-84 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - NOW-Working File E.R.A. (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - NWPC (Nat'l Women's Political Caucus)-Gay Rights, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - New Alliance Party (Fulani-Presidential Candidate), 1988 (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - PFLAG, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - PAW-People for the American Way-Bulletins, quarterly reports, 1981-84 (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - PAW--, 1982-83 (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - Philadelphia Lesbian and Gay Task Force (PLGTF), 1984 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Religious Orgs./Churches: Evangelical Religion and Homosexuality, 1980-84 (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - Religious Orgs./Churches: Religious Support-Catholic Church (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - Religious Orgs./Churches: Church of the Brethren-Civil Rights for Gays and Lesbians, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - Religious Orgs./Churches: MCC (Metropolitan Community Churches), 1979-83 (Box 12, Folder 46)
    - Religious Orgs./Churches: United Church of Christ, 1979-81 (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - Religious Orgs./Churches: United Methodist Church, 1979-84 (Box 12, Folder 48)
    - Religious Organizations/Churches-G & L Civil Rights, 1979-84 (Box 12, Folder 49)
    - R.I.S.E. Program (Raising Immune System Efficiency) (Box 12, Folder 50)
    - Right to Privacy P.A.C., 1984 (Box 12, Folder 51)
    - HRCF Southeastern Conference of Lesbians and Gay Men, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 52)
    - Trade Unionists for Human Rights, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - HIV and AIDS
    - AIDS Information-Reports (AMFAR, NYS Dept. of Health), 1985 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - AZT Testing, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - AIDS-International (Australia, Canada), 1985 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - AIDS and IV Drug Use (Report by NASADAD), 1988 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - AIDS and Employment-Economic Impacts, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - AIDS Prevention -GAO Testimony (Budget Appropriations), 1988 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - AIDS Testing - reports, statements, news, 1987-88 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Abortion Editorials (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Abortion (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Abortion (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Breast & Cervical Cancer (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Hepatitis (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Tuberculosis (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - AIDS-General (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - McClintock "AIDS Cure Act" Program (HR 3310) (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - AIDS-Nat'l Commission Report (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Infectious Disease Emergency Act of 1993 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - AIDS- Budget (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - AIDS-Education & Prevention (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - AIDS-Research (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - AIDS-Treatment (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - AIDS-Transmission (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - PWAs/HIV (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - AIDS- Editorials (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Press Clips: Misc. AIDS (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - AIDS- Healthcare workers (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Kimberly Bergalis (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - AIDS-Testing (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - AIDS-Immigration Ban (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - The Politics of AIDS I (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - The Politics of AIDS II (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Magic Johnson/ AIDS in Sports (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - AIDS/Global (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Cannabis Buying Club (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Act-up (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Women & AIDS (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Harkin (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Steve Smith's Files, 1985-1990
      - Whitman-Walker Clinic, D.C., 1984-88 (Box 13, Folder 7)
      - Washington D.C.- AIDS plans, Bills, 1985-87 (Box 13, Folder 8)
      - GAA (Gay Activist Alliance) Washington, D.C. AIDS Budget FY 89, 1985-1987 (Box 13, Folder 9)
      - Washington, D.C.- Health Bills 7-373 "Clinical Lab Act of 1987", 1985-1988 (Box 13, Folder 10)
      - Gay children- Families (folder 1 of 2), 1985-1989 (Box 13, Folder 11)
      - Gay children- Families (folder 2 of 2) Testimony, Bills, Hearings, 1985-89 (Box 13, Folder 12)
      - D.C. Metropolitan Comm. on AIDS Issues, 1985-89 (Box 13, Folder 13)
      - AIDS: DC Government, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 14)
      - D.C. Met. Comm. on AIDS issues- Pentamadene issue, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 15)
      - GAA DC AIDS Budget FY 1988 (Box 13, Folder 16)
      - McCormick v. Hechinger (wrongful termination case re: AIDS), 1988 (Box 13, Folder 17)
      - DC AIDS Prevention & Surveillance Projects Grant Application, 1988- 1989 (Box 13, Folder 18)
      - HRCF GLAA- Gay and Lesbian Activist Alliance, 1988-90 (Box 13, Folder 19)
      - D.C. Health Care Agency (proposed), 1989 (Box 13, Folder 20)
      - DC-AIDS (Fiscal Planning), 1989 (Box 13, Folder 21)
      - David Clarke et. al. v. USA (Briefs), 1989 (Box 13, Folder 22)
      - Legislation "Basic Health Benefits for all Americans", 1989 (Box 13, Folder 23)
      - DC AIDS Budget FY 1990, 1989-1990 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Military, 1984-1996
    This subseries includes information regarding the U.S. Navy's admission of Negroes in 1942.
    - Military Don't Ask Don't Tell (DA / DT) Policy, 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Military Articles, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Nunn, Sam (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - (DA / DT) Cammermeyer (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - (DA / DT) Hackworth (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - (DA / DT) Inman (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - (DA / DT) Meinhold (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - (DA / DT) Monsuma (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - (DA / DT) Panccia (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - (DA / DT) Peck (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - (DA / DT) Colin Powell (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - (DA / DT) Crae (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - (DA / DT) Steffan Decision (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - (DA / DT) Steffan (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - (DA / DT) Thome (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - (DA / DT) Truscott (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Other Countries- Military Ban (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Lesbian Veterans Press Conf. (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Military I (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Military II (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Boyer Resolution (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - To Support and Defend, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Schroeder Bill (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Military Letters (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Military- ROTC/ Recruiting (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Operation Lift the Ban Weekend (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Military Echoes of Prejudice (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Service members Legal Defense Network (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Aspin - Memo of June 1993 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Don't Ask Don't Tell (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Nunn Skelton Meehan Boxer (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Military Regulations (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Military 10-93, 11-93, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Military (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Campaign for Military Service (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Campaign for Military Service (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Military Editorials (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Military- Op- Ed Pieces and Letters to the Editor (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - 1993 Military Articles I (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - 1993 Military Articles II (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - 1993 Military Articles III (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - HRCF Meehan/ Fazio Amendment to the Defense Authorization Bill, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - HRCF-PPD Defense Authorization Bill (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - DOD's Policy on Homosexuality- published by GAO, June 1992 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Campaign for Military Service, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Gays in Military: Sen. Nunn; Hearing of the Senate Armed Services Committee, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Gays in Military- Editorial War (news clippings), 1993 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - HRCF-PPD Gays in the Military & other issues, 1993-1994 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Military & Homosexuality - Press, 1989-1992 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Military Issues- Black Lesbian and Gay (Veterans) Leadership Forum, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Military Ban on Homosexuality- Senate and House Legislation- Press Releases, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Operation Lift the Ban/ Speak Out, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Military- Post-Election press releases, 1992-1993 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - H.R. 2401 Statute Language/ Committee language, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - U.S. President/ Administration Position on Don't Ask/ Don't Tell, July 1993 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Lesbians in the Military (reports, articles), 1989-1992 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - (SecDef) Military working Group Report, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Army memo to lift the Ban, 1991-92 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Press Clips/ Editorials on DA, DT and Gay In Military, 1991-1993 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Military Briefing Materials, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Military Discharge Statistics, 1991-1995 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Military- Coast Guard, 1991-92 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Military- Sodomy- press clippings, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Military Conduct- Various (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Military- Female Harassment- Articles, Reports, clippings, 1988-94 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Operation Lift the Ban- Talking Points, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Military- APA (American Psychological Association) Packet Articles, 1990-1992 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - HRCF PPD - Equal Employment Act, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - HRCF Serial murders of gay men (reports, news, efforts), 1993 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - HRCF Gays in the Military, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - HRCF Health Care Reform Bill - sexual discrimination, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - GL MFP (Military Freedom Project), 1993-1995 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - GLBVA and related vet groups, 1992-1994 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Military-resources for vets, 1990-1992 (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Military Reading Project, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - MFP (Military Freedom Project), 1989-1993 (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - GL MFP-old minutes, 1989-1991 (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - DoD Regs-copies and related materials, 1993-1994 (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - Surveys Re: Military Ban, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - Military-Workplan/Targets, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - Issue-fact sheets (Campaign for Military Service), 1993 (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - CMS Fact Sheets, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - CMS Targeting, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - CMS Policy Recommendations, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 43)
    - Rand Report-Talking Points, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 44)
    - CRS (Congressional Research Service): Homosexuals and Military, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 45)
    - CRS Info Pack, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 46)
    - Right Wing Ban Attempts, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 47)
    - Press Clippings-Gays in the Military, 1991-1992 (Box 15, Folder 48)
    - West Point/Major Berry, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 49)
    - Military-letters from orgs opposing ban, 1991-1993 (Box 15, Folder 50)
    - APA-Meeting of National Orgs on the US Military Gay Exclusion, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 51)
    - GLMFP and Service Members Legal Defense Network, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 52)
    - Department of Defense, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 53)
    - House Armed Service Committee Members, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 54)
    - HASC, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 55)
    - HRC Talking Points-Public Policy Dept., 1993 (Box 15, Folder 56)
    - Articles-PPD, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 57)
    - Military L-6-05 Background Materials (Box 15, Folder 58)
    - Military Resolution, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 59)
    - House Bill 2440 (gays in VA Nat'l Guard), 1993 (Box 15, Folder 60)
    - Opposition to Hoar, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 61)
    - Witch Hunt-Japan, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 62)
    - Negroes in the Military, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 63)
    - Nunn's Codification, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 64)
    - DoD Military Working Group Reports (Folder 1 of 2), 1991-1993 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - DoD Military Working Group Reports (Folder 2 of 2), 1991-1993 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Military Political Cartoons re: Gays in the Military Debate (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - HRCF Notes on Policy (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Military- Freedom of Expression/ Association, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Military- Policy History, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Military Gen. Colin Powell & DA, DT Policy, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Military- Legal Issues (reports, articles) (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - U.S. Congress Republican Hearings, Dec 1992 (Box 16, Folder 9)